http://www.northwestcellars.com/policies.html

Our Kirkland tasting room is now open. Make a reservation. New Hours
Menu
Wines Red WinesWhite and Rosé Wines Wines ArchiveWhere to buyAwardsArtist SeriesGifts & AccessoriesWine & Food PairingsCellar Rats Wine ClubTestimonialsLabels Customize Your LabelWine Label Gallery Corporate Gifts Wine Labels Hotel & Restaurant Wine LabelsNon-Profit & Fundraisers Wine Labels Weddings & AnniversariesBirthday Wine LabelsHoliday Wine LabelsMiscellaneous Wine LabelsGifts Corporate Wine GiftsBusiness Wine GiftsCustom Wine GiftsWedding Wine GiftsBirthday Wine GiftsAnniversary Wine GiftsHoliday Wine GiftsEvents  Upcoming EventsEvent Sign-upEvent SpaceWineriesFundraisers Wine FundraisingSchool FundraisingProcessTasting Room KirklandContactBlogAbout Us Leave a Review
Shopping Cart   Items:
Subtotal:
Checkout
|
Customer Center
Search
Wines
Red Wines
White and Rosé Wines
Wines Archive
— Leave a Review
With Northwest Cellars, your wine truly reflects your good taste.
Home
Policies
Get More Information  Shop for Wine  Make A Wine Tasting Reservation
Policies
Privacy Policy
At Northwest Cellars, we recognize and respect our customers' privacy. We diligently protect the trust you have placed in us. We have developed a Privacy Policy to assure you that the information collected about you is only what is needed for conducting business and offering products and services that might be of interest to you.
Our Policy
Federal and Washington state law requires us to request identification from each consumer to prove that you are of age to legally purchase alcohol. To process an order, we need your name, home or other physical address, including street name and name of city or town, email address, telephone number, date of birth and credit card number. We understand the sensitivity of this information and maintain our files on a secured server to protect against unauthorized access. In addition to obtaining personal information, we may collect tracking information for statistical purposes, which is disclosed to third parties for statistical purposes only. This aggregate information is for statistical purposes only. It is for understanding consumer trends and does not contain any personal information about you. WE DO NOT AND WILL NOT, UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES, SELL PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANYONE FOR ANY PURPOSE.
Personal Information and Data Gathering
Northwest Cellars often uses third-party development partners to assist in online development and deployment as well as in data and information collection. These companies are strictly bound by our privacy policy covered below, as well as by all other conventions and business practices of Northwest Cellars concerning user information and data from online sources. For the purposes of this document, the terms "We," "Us" and Northwest Cellars will also represent these third-party developers.
We collect anonymous information from visits to our site to help us understand the usage patterns of our site, and to provide better customer service. Information collected in this manner is provided automatically by your system and the systems that you use to connect to our site. For example, we keep track of what time people enter our site, how long they stay on the site, and what sections they visit on the site. This information is kept in aggregate, anonymous format. We use this information to better tailor our site for our visitors and their usage patterns, as well as to gauge performance and other measures of the site, again in anonymous and aggregate format.
Cookies are sometimes used to further track usage patterns of the site by users, in aggregate and anonymous format. Cookies left on your system by our site are sometimes used for the purpose of allowing users the convenience of not having to re-enter usernames and passwords on our site, however, no username or password information is kept on your local machine. Only a unique identifier is kept on your system that will allow you to access the records stored on our secure, password-protected server(s). No financial or personal information will ever be left on your system in the form of a cookie.
Registration is required to use certain features of our site. We will collect general contact information, such as name and e-mail address, as well as demographic information, such as age, gender and zip code. Data collected from online user-completed forms is stored in secure, encrypted, password protected server locations. Demographic information collected is used to help us, or our partners, to analyze our aggregate user base and better tailor our site, promotions or other features to better serve that user base. Contact information is also used to better understand our user base.
From time to time, Northwest Cellars will contact our registered users who have opted in to be e-mailed with promotional information that we feel would be applicable to, and desired by that user. At any time a user wishes to opt-out of these e-mails, an opt-out link is provided in the email. Once opted-out, the user will not receive any further communication from us, aside from any system messages that are necessary to that user in specific transactions, such as e-commerce order summaries.
Further use of personal information and data gathered by Northwest Cellars.
Northwest Cellars will occasionally utilize partners and vendors to assist it in analysis of the data and information collected by our sites. This information is used in aggregate and anonymous format for the purpose of better tailoring our website, promotions or other company endeavors to better suit our user base. This information is shared with our partners and vendors only on an as-needed basis. Financial information will never be shared with any organization other than those necessary for completing the financial transaction required.
Information and data gathered solely by Northwest Cellars will never be sold, traded or shared with third-parties.
This site may contain links to other sites. Northwest Cellars is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Public Forums
This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We also encourage visitors to be courteous in communicating with others and to be smart about choosing when and to whom to release personal information online. Never disclose any personal information that is of a sensitive or confidential nature on any public area of our site.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All registration information is stored in secure locations on encrypted, password-protected servers.
Online Store Policies
Shipments of Wine
Due to legal restrictions on shipments of wine and other alcoholic beverages, we are only permitted to ship to the States that allow Direct-to-Consumer shipping of alcohol. Contact us at info@northwestcellars.com if you have a question about your State.
All wine orders must be placed by a person 21 years of age or older. Verification of age is required at the time of delivery. We recommend use of a business address to facilitate delivery of your purchase. Wine will not be delivered to a visibly intoxicated person. Failure to produce age verification forfeits the right to receive the shipment until identification is produced. In such circumstances, the order may be held in storage at a local depot of the shipping company until appropriate identification is produced, or it may be shipped back to the winery. All associated costs will be the responsibility of and be charged to the customer.
Shipping will normally be by Fedex Ground, and will take between 1-7 days depending on your location. We do not ship outside the United States. Shipping is difficult in the summer and winter because of the weather – we will do our best to complete and ship your order during these times.
Refund Policy
If the wine is faulty, we will replace it, but not if it is due to overheating or freezing during shipping. In this case, your claim would be with Fedex.
Inquiries
If you have a questions, please email info@northwestcellars.com .
Sign up for the latest updates
Don’t miss out on events, discounts, and sales
*By signing up for phone text messages you agree to your own carrier charges.
Rest assured, we never share your information.
WinesCustom Wine LabelsWine GiftsOrder Wine and LabelWine Label FAQsArt SpecificationsOccasionsWineriesFundraisers
About UsNewsPressReviewsNewsletterTerms of UsePoliciesTrademarksSitemap
Visit Northwest Cellars Winery Tasting Room
Monday:
closed
Tuesday.:
closed
Wednesday:
closed
Thursday:
1-6
Friday:
1-6
Saturday:
12-6
Sunday:
12-5
Contact Us!
Northwest Cellars Winery, Totem Square, 11909 124th Avenue, NE, Kirkland, WA 98034 | Ph: 425.825.9463
© 2004 – 2020 Northwest Cellars
